asungur.com

sunguralican@gmail.com

22C Oxford Road London, N4 3EY

I am a full-stack software developer based in London.

I am a studious learner and I believe in writing clean, readable code with comprehensive documentation.

I have multiple years of experience developing full stack applications and back-end development projects using Ruby, Rails, SQL, JavaScript and React, Git, Linux and RESTful APIs.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## Full-stack Web Developer, Self-employed

2019 - Present

- Development of open source web applications using Ruby, Node.js, PostgreSQL, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, Rails, React.js
- Trend-check: A dashboard application retrieves and visualizes the top Twitter trends in the UK. (Ruby + Sinatra, TwitterAPI, GoogleCharts, HTML, CSS)
- · Post-it: A Reddit-like application with discussions and upvoting features. (Rails)
- · Hop-timer: A user-friendly benchmarking Ruby gem.

Academic Consultant 2016 - Present

- · Oxford Brooks University(2016-2017) and AA School of Architecture(2017-Present)
- Teaching procedural modelling, geometry rationalisation, digital fabrication and environmental/structural analysis techniques to MArch and MSc students at EmTech Studio.

Architectural Designer 2017 - 2020

- · Pattern Design(2017-2018), WilkinsonEyre(2018-present), London
- HS2 Old Oak Common: High-speed transport project in London
- · Qatar Foundation and Al Rayyan Stadiums: World stadiums in Qatar
- Developed Dynamo and Grasshopper3D scripts
- · Automation of model transfer, scheduling, clash detection using Python and C# script editing in RhinoSDK.
- Geometrical rationalisation of doubly/singly curved geometry for structural, cost and environmental efficiencies.
- · Project coordination with engineering disciplines and manufacturers.

## **EDUCATION**

Launch School Remote | 2019-2020

Multi-year full-stack Software Engineering curriculum Ruby, Node.js, HTTP, PostgreSQL | HTML, CSS, JavaScript

https://launchschool.com/employers

**Architectural Association School of Architecture** 

London | 2014-2016

Master of Architecture, Distinction, Emergent Technologies & Design

Middle East Technical University

Ankara | 2009-2014

**Bachelor of Architecture** 

## **SKILLS**

Languages	Frameworks	Technologies
Ruby	Erb	Git/Github
SQL	Ruby on Rails	HTTP
Node.js	Sinatra	PostgreSQL
JavaScript	React.js	Redis
CSS, HTML	Redux	REST APIs
Python		